<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laurine Huber</title>
    <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Laurine Huber</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 22:53:43 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://laurinehu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MALOTEC Seminars</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/others/malotec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 22:53:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/others/malotec/</guid>
      <description>I was happy to present several works in the context of our regular team meetings.
https://malotec.loria.fr/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Alignment Cost-Based Classification of Log Traces Using Machine-Learning</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/ml4pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/ml4pm/</guid>
      <description>Conformance checking is an important aspect of process mining that identifies the differences between the behaviors recorded in a log and those exhibited by an associated process model. Machine learning and deep learning methods perform extremely well in sequence analysis. We successfully apply both a Recurrent Neural Network and a Random Forest classifier to the problem of evaluating whether the alignment cost of a log trace to a process model is below an arbitrary threshold, and provide a lower bound for the fitness of the process model based on the classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Sentence Embeddings Capture Discourse Properties of Sentences from Scientific Abstracts</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/codi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/codi/</guid>
      <description>We introduce four tasks designed to determine which sentence encoders best capture discourse properties of sentences from scientific abstracts, namely coherence between clauses of a sentence, and discourse relations within sentences. We show that even if contextual encoders such as BERT or SciBERT encodes the coherence in discourse units, they do not help to predict three discourse relations commonly used in scientific abstracts. We discuss what these results underline, namely that these discourse relations are based on particular phrasing that allow non-contextual encoders to perform well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Co-Chair of RECITAL 2020 !</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/others/recital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 22:53:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/others/recital/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m happy to be part of the organizing comitee of RECITAL, co-located (virtually) with JEP and TALN 2020. The conference JEP-TALN-RECITAL 2020 will be held online from 8 to 19 June.
https://jep-taln2020.loria.fr/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD student day of the NLPKD department</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/others/phdday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 22:53:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/others/phdday/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m happy to co-organize the PhD Student day of the Natural Language Processing and Knowledge Discovery Department of our laboratory. This day will be the opportunity for all students to present their work.
https://www.loria.fr/en/research/departments/natural-language-processing-and-knowledge-discovery/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alignement de Structures Argumentatives et Discursives par Fouille de Graphes et de Redescriptions</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/sfc2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/sfc2019/</guid>
      <description>Dans cet article, nous étudions la similarité entre structures argumentatives et discursives en alignant des sous-arbres dans un corpus annoté en RST et en structure argumentative. Contrairement aux travaux précédents, nous nenous intéressons pas uniquement à un alignement relation à relation, mais à unalignement de sous-structures. À l’aide de méthodes de fouille de données, nous montrons que des similitudes existent entre l’argumentation et le discours. L’annotation multiple du corpus permet également de proposer un alignement entreles structures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Discourse and Argumentation Structures using Subtrees and Redescription Mining</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/argmining2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/argmining2019/</guid>
      <description>In this paper, we investigate similarities between discourse and argumentation structures by aligning subtrees in a corpus containing both annotations. Contrary to previous works, we focus on comparing sub-structures and not only relation matches. Using data mining techniques , we show that discourse and argumen-tation most often align well, and the double annotation allows to derive a mapping between structures. Moreover, this approach enables the study of similarities between discourse structures and differences in their expressive power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOC-poset of discourse and argumentation: what can we learn on their dependencies?</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/cla2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/cla2020/</guid>
      <description>We aim at finding and understanding dependencies between linguistic structures which differ in terms of constraints and expressive power. It has been shown that studying dependencies between the argu- mentation structure (ARG) and the Rhetorical Structure Theory (RST) is non-trivial and requires a fine methodology. In this paper, we propose to take advantage of the AOC-Poset structure to understand how the subgraphs alignements occur in a small corpus annotated in ARG and RST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>👩‍💻 laurine [dot] huber [at] loria [dot] fr
📭 Bureau B150
Campus Scientifique, 615 Rue du Jardin-Botanique
54506 Vandœuvre-lès-Nancy</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>