<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Laurine Huber</title>
    <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Laurine Huber</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 11:26:27 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alignement de Structures Argumentatives et Discursives par Fouille de Graphes et de Redescriptions</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/sfc2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/sfc2019/</guid>
      <description>Dans cet article, nous étudions la similarité entre structures argumentatives et discursives en alignant des sous-arbres dans un corpus annoté en RST et en structure argumentative. Contrairement aux travaux précédents, nous nenous intéressons pas uniquement à un alignement relation à relation, mais à unalignement de sous-structures. À l’aide de méthodes de fouille de données, nous montrons que des similitudes existent entre l’argumentation et le discours. L’annotation multiple du corpus permet également de proposer un alignement entreles structures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Discourse and Argumentation Structures using Subtrees and Redescription Mining</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/argmining2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/argmining2019/</guid>
      <description>In this paper, we investigate similarities between discourse and argumentation structures by aligning subtrees in a corpus containing both annotations. Contrary to previous works, we focus on comparing sub-structures and not only relation matches. Using data mining techniques , we show that discourse and argumen-tation most often align well, and the double annotation allows to derive a mapping between structures. Moreover, this approach enables the study of similarities between discourse structures and differences in their expressive power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOC-poset of discourse and argumentation: what can we learn on their dependencies?</title>
      <link>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/cla2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 11:26:27 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laurinehu.github.io/publications/cla2020/</guid>
      <description>We aim at finding and understanding dependencies between linguistic structures which differ in terms of constraints and expressive power. It has been shown that studying dependencies between the argu- mentation structure (ARG) and the Rhetorical Structure Theory (RST) is non-trivial and requires a fine methodology. In this paper, we propose to take advantage of the AOC-Poset structure to understand how the subgraphs alignements occur in a small corpus annotated in ARG and RST.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>